(Amy:)Where would I have picked up
an alien parasite?
(Howard:)There you are.
(Raj:)Oh, hey.
(Howard:)Let me ask you a question.
What are you most afraid of?
(Raj:)I don't know. Um...
(Raj:)Nuclear war.
(Raj:)Accidentally being
buried alive.
(Raj:)Any of those movies where
you get that phone call
(Raj:)that says you're
going to die.
(Raj:)And then you do.
(Howard:)No. Something very specific
(Howard:)that we both know you,
(Howard:)Rajesh Koothrappali,
are terrified of.
(Raj:)Well, type two diabetes
runs in my family.
(Raj:)The thought of
losing a toe...
(Howard:)Spiders!
You're afraid of spiders!
(Raj:)What the heck is this?
(Howard:)A jar with a big spider
in it, of course.
(Howard:)Bravery test.
(Howard:)First one to take his hand out
is the sidekick.
(Raj:)Are you crazy?
(Howard:)Perhaps.
(Howard:)Are you scared?
(Raj:)No. But it's a stupid test.
(Howard:)Oh, really?
What if the earth was in danger
(Howard:)and the only way to save it was
(Howard:)to stick your hand
in a jar with a spider?